{
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@gmail.com",
      "role": "professor",
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "users": [],
  "professor": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "questions": [],
      "name": "",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Mathematique",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "25+1",
          "answer1": "2",
          "answer2": "26",
          "answer3": "4",
          "answer4": "5",
          "correct": "26"
        },
        {
          "question": "1/1",
          "answer1": "1",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "8",
          "correct": "1"
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "eee",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "eeeeeeeeee",
          "answer1": "eeeeee",
          "answer2": "eeeeee",
          "answer3": "eeeeeeeee",
          "answer4": "eeeee",
          "correct": "eeeee"
        }
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "aaaaaaaaa",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "answer1": "aaaaaa",
          "answer2": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "answer3": "aaaaa",
          "answer4": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "correct": "aaaaaa"
        }
      ],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "aaaaaaaaa",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "answer1": "aaaaaa",
          "answer2": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "answer3": "aaaaa",
          "answer4": "aaaaaaaaa",
          "correct": "aaaaaa"
        }
      ],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "Math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "12",
          "answer1": "55",
          "answer2": "2",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "5",
          "correct": "5"
        }
      ],
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "name": "Math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "12",
          "answer1": "55",
          "answer2": "2",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "5",
          "correct": "5"
        }
      ],
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "Math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "2+2",
          "answer1": "4",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "12",
          "correct": "4"
        }
      ],
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "name": "Math",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "2+2",
          "answer1": "4",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "12",
          "correct": "4"
        }
      ],
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "name": "fresh",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Caluculer",
          "answer1": "a",
          "answer2": "b",
          "answer3": "c",
          "answer4": "d",
          "correct": "d"
        }
      ],
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "Mathematique",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "1+2",
          "answer1": "2",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "3",
          "answer4": "3",
          "correct": "3"
        },
        {
          "question": "5*5",
          "answer1": "25",
          "answer2": "6",
          "answer3": "67",
          "answer4": "21",
          "correct": "21"
        }
      ],
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "name": "Mathematique",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "25+1",
          "answer1": "2",
          "answer2": "26",
          "answer3": "4",
          "answer4": "5",
          "correct": "26"
        },
        {
          "question": "1/1",
          "answer1": "1",
          "answer2": "3",
          "answer3": "5",
          "answer4": "8",
          "correct": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "2*5",
          "answer1": "2",
          "answer2": "5",
          "answer3": "10",
          "answer4": "2",
          "correct": "10"
        }
      ],
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "name": "Ahmed",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "djldj",
          "answer1": "mlmkk",
          "answer2": "kjkjkj",
          "answer3": "lji",
          "answer4": "kllk",
          "correct": "kllk"
        }
      ],
      "id": 13
    }
  ],
  "students": [
    {
      "username": "Ahmed",
      "email": "ahmed@gmail.com",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "Ahmed",
      "email": "Bouzid@gal",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "username": "aaa",
      "email": "aaa@g",
      "password": "aaa",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "username": "lllll",
      "email": "aaaa@mgm",
      "password": "aaa",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "username": "Ahled",
      "email": "hjzk@f",
      "password": "Ahmed",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "username": "ahmed",
      "email": "aldzlz@l",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "username": "ahmam",
      "email": "kka@ss",
      "password": "123",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "username": "ahle",
      "email": "aaa@a",
      "password": "aaa",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "username": "zzzzzzzzzzzzzzz",
      "email": "admin@gmail.2com",
      "password": "zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz",
      "id": 9
    }
  ]
}